hey everyone Juby here today I've got some incredibly exciting news to share
with y'all we're gearing up to make a real difference in people's lives and I
can't wait to get started we're announcing our very own twitch
donation marathon in partnership with the American Heart Association it's for
a great cause and I'd love for you all to join us every 40 seconds someone
somewhere has a heart attack or stroke together we can make a significant
impact on this global issue and break down the health equity gap because
everyone should have quality health care access so come by my twitch on
September 28th at 4 p.m. CST it's going to be a gaming marathon filled with fun
mystery boxes and some very interesting incentives trust me you won't want to
miss it and of course the most crucial part is donating to the American Heart
Association to donate simply visit the Tiltify link in the description below
or just comment charity in the chat during the stream every dollar makes a
difference so let's make this event a huge success I also want to take a
moment to thank you all for being such an amazing community your support means
the world to me and I know that together we can do some real good in this world
so I hope y'all can join us on the 28th for a day of gaming laughter and giving
back let's make a real impact and show the world what our community can do
until then I hope you guys take care and have a wonderful day bye